<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Belgian Bitcoin Association]]></title>
  <link href="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//"/>
  <updated>2016-11-03T09:32:56+01:00</updated>
  <id>http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Belgian Bitcoin Association]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[info@bitcoinassociation.be]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin discussed at the European Banking Association]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/10/22/bitcoin-discussed-at-the-european-banking-association/"/>
    <updated>2014-10-22T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/10/22/bitcoin-discussed-at-the-european-banking-association</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Jérémie Dubois-Lacoste and Jean Wallemacq, both <a href="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/#/about">directors at the Belgian Bitcoin Association</a>, introduced cryptocurrencies at the Working Group on Electronic Alternative Payments of the <a href="https://www.abe-eba.eu/Home-N=HomeEBA-L=EN.aspx">Euro Banking Association</a> on October 22nd.</p>

<p>Topics included: General introduction to Bitcoin &amp; to the blockchain technology, alternative cryptocurrencies, notary use of the blockchain and other, non-traditional, use of the blockchain technology.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin presented at the Katholieke Hogeschool Limburg]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/10/21/bitcoin-presented-at-the-katholieke-hogeschool-limburg/"/>
    <updated>2014-10-21T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/10/21/bitcoin-presented-at-the-katholieke-hogeschool-limburg</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Chris D’Costa, <a href="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/#/about">director at the Belgian Bitcoin Association</a>, was a featured speaker at the &ldquo;Bank of the Future&rdquo; workshop held on October 21st at the <a href="http://www.khlim.be/">Katholieke Hogeschool Limburg</a>.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The mother of all cryptocurrency meetups]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/10/18/the-mother-of-all-cryptocurrency-meetups/"/>
    <updated>2014-10-18T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/10/18/the-mother-of-all-cryptocurrency-meetups</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The Belgian Bitcoin Association co-organized <a href="http://www.meetup.com/Bitcoin-Brussels/events/208626782/">The mother of all cryptocurrency meetups</a> in Antwerpen on October 18th.  People from three Belgian Bitcoin meetups (Antwerpen, Brussels, Ghent) gathered for a great afternoon (and some more additional drinks afterwards…).</p>

<p>Topics addressed included: pizza &amp; sushi ordering with Bitcoin, presentation &amp; support to Ghent Bitcoin Boulevard, Frank Bass and Bitcoin Adoption, Trezor Demo, Q&amp;A &ndash; Belgian Bitcoin Association.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin session at the Belgian Finance Club]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/10/15/bitcoin-session-at-the-belgian-finance-club/"/>
    <updated>2014-10-15T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/10/15/bitcoin-session-at-the-belgian-finance-club</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Thomas Spaas, Jérémie Dubois-Lacoste, <a href="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/#/about">directors at the Belgian Bitcoin Association</a>, and David Boveington-Fauran, <a href="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/#/members">member of the Belgian Bitcoin Association</a> and <a href="http://www.ebtm.be">founder of EBTM</a>, were speakers at the Belgian Finance Club on <a href="http://emailing.synchrone.be/t/ViewEmail/t/3A52E005C79BECA5/1FCBF988B467E4A1D9767B6002735221">October 15th</a>.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[EURO BITCOIN postponed]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/10/02/euro-bitcoin-postponed/"/>
    <updated>2014-10-02T13:41:21+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/10/02/euro-bitcoin-postponed</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The &ldquo;Euro Bitcoin&rdquo; conference scheduled to take place on October 8th in Paris has been postponed.
According to <a href="http://bitcoin-france.org/2014/10/01/conference-euro-bitcoin-reportee-2015/">French association</a>, the conference will take place beginning of 2015.
If you bought your ticket already, you will be of course reimbursed.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[EURO BITCOIN: The first French-speaking Bitcoin conference in Europe]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/09/15/the-first-french-speaking-bitcoin-conference-in-europe/"/>
    <updated>2014-09-15T19:01:40+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/09/15/the-first-french-speaking-bitcoin-conference-in-europe</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//images/euro-bitcoin-avatar.jpg" width="250" height="250"></p>

<p>The first french-speaking Bitcoin conference in Europe will take place in Paris on October 8th, 2014.
<a href="http://eurobitcoin.org">Euro Bitcoin</a> will be held at the Bibliothèque François Mitterrand (BNF).</p>

<p>The event is organized by the <a href="http://bitcoin-france.org">Association Bitcoin France</a>, with the support of the Belgian Bitcoin Association and the <a href="http://bitcoinassociation.ch">Swiss Bitcoin Association Switzerland</a>.
It will feature an interesting pannel of speakers from various horizon (both inside and outside the bitcoin community), both in French and English.</p>

<p>If you are a business, there are still few sponsorship opportunities open.</p>

<p>You can <strong>get a discount as a BBA member</strong>, contact us for more information.
The Belgian Bitcoin Association may also organize a joint trip to attend the event if enough people are interested, don&rsquo;t hesitate to get in touch with us!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin 2 Business Congress Brussels taking place on 16-17 October]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/09/15/bitcoin-2-business-congress-brussels-taking-place-on-16-17-october/"/>
    <updated>2014-09-15T17:16:43+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/09/15/bitcoin-2-business-congress-brussels-taking-place-on-16-17-october</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//images/btc2b_logo.png" width="720" height="200"></p>

<p>Brussels will host one of the major Bitcoin events in Europe. Bitcoin 2 Business Congress will focus on the Start-up show, B2B meetings, debates, speeches by well-known speakers such as Matthew Roszak, Vitalik Buterin, Jacob Hansen, Brett Stapper and many others. Get more info at the website <a href="http://www.btc2b.com">www.btc2b.com</a> or contact <a href="mailto:congress@btc2b.com">congress@btc2b.com</a> in case of any questions.</p>

<p>There is also discount code for BBA members, contact us or <a href="mailto:congress@btc2b.com">congress@btc2b.com</a> for more info.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Again, an extended feature on Bitcoin in L'Echo]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/06/07/again/"/>
    <updated>2014-06-07T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/06/07/again</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A 2-page feature in <a href="http://www.lecho.be/r/t/1/id/9510610">L&#8217;Echo</a>, with title: &ldquo;Bitcoin La révolution est en marche&rdquo;.  Jérémie Dubois-Lacoste is interviewed and voices a <a href="http://www.lecho.be/r/t/1/id/9510614">strong opinion</a>: &ldquo;Les monnaies classiques ont perdu leur crédibilité&rdquo;.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin 2014 Conference]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/05/14/bitcoin-2014-conference/"/>
    <updated>2014-05-14T15:23:59+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/05/14/bitcoin-2014-conference</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>All Directors of the Belgian Bitcoin Association will attend the May 15th-17th <a href="http://bitcoin2014.com">#Bitcoin2014</a> conference in Amsterdam. Some Directors will join a pre-conference roundtable meeting of European digital currency groups and associations.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin explained at TriFinance]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/05/12/bitcoin-explained-at-trifinance/"/>
    <updated>2014-05-12T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/05/12/bitcoin-explained-at-trifinance</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Thomas Spaas and Jean Wallemacq present Bitcoin, its relevance, its working, merchants accepting it in Belgium, along with some of the fiscal, legal, regulatory &amp; overall challenges associated with Bitcoin, at <a href="http://www.trifinance.be">TriFinance</a>.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin explained at Rotary-Bruxelles-Sud]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/05/07/bitcoin-explained-at-rotary-bruxelles-sud/"/>
    <updated>2014-05-07T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/05/07/bitcoin-explained-at-rotary-bruxelles-sud</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Jean Wallemacq presents Bitcoin, its relevance, its working, merchants accepting it in Belgium, along with some of the challenges associated with Bitcoin, at the Bruxelles-Sud chapter of Rotary.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thomas Spaas' TEDx talk in Hasselt]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/04/01/thomas-spaas-tedx-talk-in-hasselt/"/>
    <updated>2014-04-01T11:32:10+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/04/01/thomas-spaas-tedx-talk-in-hasselt</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Thomas Spaas gave a Tedx talk on tedxuhasselt, about the relation between bitcoin and human rights (video online soon)</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our new blog]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/03/28/new-blog/"/>
    <updated>2014-03-28T11:21:20+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/03/28/new-blog</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>So, this is our new blog. We will be re-posting all older news
here, backdated. More to come!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Association mentioned on CoinDesk]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/03/27/association-mentioned-on-coindesk/"/>
    <updated>2014-03-27T23:08:30+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/03/27/association-mentioned-on-coindesk</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The Belgian Bitcoin Association was mentioned in the recent <a href="http://www.coindesk.com/swarm-intelligence-event-first-science-conference-accept-bitcoin/">CoinDesk article</a> regarding the scientific conference organized at the ULB. In the article, <em>Arne Brutschy</em> explains the reason why the organizers decided to accept bitcoin for conference registrations.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin accepted by Belgian scientific conference]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/03/17/bitcoin-accepted-by-belgian-scientific-conference/"/>
    <updated>2014-03-17T22:28:56+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/03/17/bitcoin-accepted-by-belgian-scientific-conference</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The Belgian Bitcoin Association is proud to announce that the local scientific conference for swarm intelligence is now accepting bitcoin!</p>

<div class="embed-video-container"><iframe width="480" height="360" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/vjJ02KDfG2o " frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></div>




<!-- more -->


<p>Nederlandstalige versie zie hieronder
English version see below</p>

<h4>Version française</h4>

<p><a href="http://iridia.ulb.ac.be/">IRIDIA</a> est un laboratoire de <a href="http://www.ulb.ac.be">l’Université Libre de Bruxelles</a> et leader en intelligence artificielle.
Les chercheurs au sein d’IRIDIA étudient les systèmes décentralisés et auto-organisés, comme des groupes de robots imitant les insectes sociaux. Le concept novateur de bitcoin est par conséquent d’un grand intéret pour le groupe de recherche.</p>

<p>IRIDIA a été l’un des principaux incubateurs de la scène bitcoin belge. Au laboratoire, certains chercheurs ont crée un groupe de discussion régulier, qui est plus tard devenu le “meetup groupe” de Bruxelles, l’un des plus anciens dans le monde et des plus importants en Europe. Le groupe, à son tour, fut un catalyseur majeur pour la création de l’association nationale récemment établie: la <a href="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/">Belgian Bitcoin Association</a>.</p>

<p>IRIDIA organise bi-annuellement la principale conférence internationale sur la swarm intelligence (l’intelligence en essaim): <a href="http://iridia.ulb.ac.be/ants2014">ANTS</a>.  Aujourd’hui, IRIDIA, en collaboration avec la Belgian Bitcoin Association, est fière d’annoncer que l’édition de cette année de la conférence acceptera bitcoin comme moyen de paiement pour les inscriptions. Cela fait de ANTS la première conférence scientifique à accepter bitcoin.</p>

<hr />

<h4>Nederlandstalige versie</h4>

<p><a href="http://iridia.ulb.ac.be/">IRIDIA</a> is een gerenomeerd artificieel intelligentie laboratorium, gevestigd aan de <a href="http://www.ulb.ac.be">Université Libre de Bruxelles</a>, in Brussel, België. De onderzoekers van IRIDIA bestuderen zelf-organiserende, gedecentraliseerde systemen zoals zwermen robots. Hierdoor is er vanuit de onderzoeksgroep dan ook grote interesse in het Bitcoin concept.
IRIDIA was ook een van de eerste en grootste incubators van de Belgische Bitcoin scene. In het lab startten enkele onderzoekers een discussiegroep, die later evolueerde in de &ldquo;Brussels Bitcoin meetup group&rdquo;. Een van de oudste in de wereld en grootste in Europa. Die groep was op zich een belangrijke catalysator in de creatie van de recent opgerichte <a href="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/">Belgian Bitcoin Association</a>.</p>

<p>IRIDIA organiseert tweejaarlijks de belangrijkste internationale conferentie over zwerm intelligentie: <a href="http://iridia.ulb.ac.be/ants2014">ANTS</a>. Vandaag is IRIDIA, in samenwerking met de Belgian Bitcoin Association, trots u te kunnen meedelen dat de conferentie dit jaar ook Bitcoins accepteert als betaalmiddel voor de registratie. Dit maakt dat ANTS de eerste wetenschappelijke conferentie is die Bitcoins aanvaard.</p>

<hr />

<h4>English version</h4>

<p><a href="http://iridia.ulb.ac.be/">IRIDIA</a> is a leading artificial intelligence lab, located at the <a href="http://www.ulb.ac.be">Université Libre de Bruxelles</a>, in Brussels, Belgium. Researchers at IRIDIA study self-organizing, decentralized systems such as swarms of robots. The Bitcoin concept is therefore of great interest to the research group.</p>

<p>IRIDIA was also one of the main incubators in the Belgian bitcoin scene. At the lab, some researchers created a discussion group, that later evolved into the Brussels meetup group, one of the oldest in the world and biggest in Europe. The Brussels meetup group in turn was a major catalyst in the creation of the recently established <a href="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/">Belgian Bitcoin Association</a>.</p>

<p>IRIDIA organizes bi-annually the leading international conference on swarm intelligence: <a href="http://iridia.ulb.ac.be/ants2014">ANTS</a>. Today, IRIDIA, in collaboration with the Belgian Bitcoin Association, is proud to announce this year’s edition of its conference will accept bitcoin as payment for registration. This makes ANTS the first scientific conference to accept bitcoin.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[L'Echo extended feature on bitcoin]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/03/01/lecho-extended-feature-on-bitcoin/"/>
    <updated>2014-03-01T22:26:33+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/03/01/lecho-extended-feature-on-bitcoin</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.lecho.be/r/t/1/id/9473272">Extended feature in L&#8217;Echo</a> about usage of bitcoin in Belgium and abroad. <em>Jérémie Dubois-Lacoste</em> and <em>Jean Wallemacq</em> interviewed. The bitcoin protocol is discussed as well.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The MtGox crisis]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/02/26/the-mtgox-crisis/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-26T22:24:42+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/02/26/the-mtgox-crisis</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.tijd.be/nieuws/archief/Grootste_bitcoinbeurs_verdwijnt_in_het_niets.9471436-1615.art?highlight=bitcoin">De Tijd writes</a> about the MtGox crisis. <em>Thomas Spaas</em> answers a few questions.</p>

<p><a href="http://www.lecho.be/r/t/1/id/9471513">L&#8217;Echo writes</a> about the MtGox crisis and the intact confidence of the Belgian Bitcoin community. <em>Jean Wallemacq</em> voices the stance of the Belgian Bitcoin Association.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Possible insolvency of MtGox]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/02/25/possible-insolvency-of-mtgox/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-25T22:16:19+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/02/25/possible-insolvency-of-mtgox</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is the official press release of the Belgian Bitcoin Association regarding the possible insolvency of MtGox.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>NL text: see below</p>

<h4>Version française</h4>

<p>La Belgian Bitcoin Association a appris aujourd&#8217;hui que MtGox, une des premières plateformes permettant d&#8217;acheter et de vendre des bitcoins, a suspendu ses activités, et qu&#8217;elle ne serait peut-être pas en mesure de rembourser les dépôts en dollars et en bitcoins de ses clients.</p>

<p>Même si le volume d&#8217;échange sur MtGox avait fortement diminué ces derniers temps, il est évident que la perte de confiance provoquée par cette situation aura des répercussions négatives sur la communauté Bitcoin en général.</p>

<p>Dans ce contexte, la Belgian Bitcoin Association tient à insister sur les points suivants :</p>

<ol>
<li>Les problèmes de MtGox ont été causés par une implémentation fautive de son logiciel de trading et par de graves erreurs de management de la société, et non par une erreur dans le protocole Bitcoin lui-même. Ce dernier fait l&#8217;objet d&#8217;un examen scrupuleux par d&#8217;innombrables volontaires partout dans le monde, et est constamment amélioré.</li>
<li>De nombreuses autres plateformes d&#8217;échange, certainement plus fiables, existent et sont prêtes à prendre le relai. Nous faisons ici référence à une communication émise il y a quelques heures par certaines d&#8217;entre elles : <a href="http://blog.coinbase.com/post/77766809700/joint-statement-regarding-mtgox.">http://blog.coinbase.com/post/77766809700/joint-statement-regarding-mtgox.</a></li>
<li>Nous voulons également signaler qu&#8217;il existe en Europe, notamment en Allemagne, des plateformes d&#8217;échange pour lesquelles les autorités ont imposé des normes minimales et qui inspirent dès lors plus confiance. Elles connaîtront donc vraisemblablement plus de succès.</li>
<li>La Belgian Bitcoin Association se propose de soutenir les Belges dupés par MtGox en les mettant en contact avec des experts qui peuvent leur donner un support juridique dans une procédure éventuelle contre MtGox.</li>
</ol>


<hr />

<h4>Nederlandstalige versie</h4>

<p>De Belgian Bitcoin Association vernam vandaag dat MtGox, een van de eerste websites waarop het publiek bitcoins kon kopen, haar activiteiten staakt, en misschien niet in staat zouden zijn om de deposito&rsquo;s van haar klanten, zowel in bitcoins als in dollars en euros, terug te bezorgen.</p>

<p>Hoewel de handel op het platform van MtGox het laatste half jaar niet veel meer betekende, is het evident dat de vertrouwensbreuk die MtGox heeft veroorzaakt, negatief afstraalt op de bitcoin-gemeenschap als geheel.</p>

<p>In dit licht wenst de Belgian Bitcoin Association het volgende te benadrukken.</p>

<ol>
<li>De problemen bij MtGox werden veroorzaakt door een foute implementatie van de specifieke beurssoftware van deze website en vooral door het slechte management van dit bedrijf, en niet door een fout in het bitcoinprotocol zelf, dat elke dag wordt nagekeken en verbeterd door talloze vrijwilligers over de hele wereld.</li>
<li>Talrijke, meer betrouwbare ondernemingen dan MtGox staan klaar om de rol van bitcoin exchange over te nemen. Wij verwijzen hierbij naar het bericht dat enkele grote bitcoin-bedrijven enkele uren geleden gezamenlijk vrijgegeven hebben <a href="http://blog.coinbase.com/post/77766809700/joint-statement-regarding-mtgox.">http://blog.coinbase.com/post/77766809700/joint-statement-regarding-mtgox.</a></li>
<li>Wij wensen er eveneens op te wijzen dat er ook in Europa (m.n. Duitsland) bitcoin-beursplatformen aanwezig zijn waaraan de overheid bepaalde minimumvereisten heeft opgelegd en die aldus van meer vertrouwen kunnen genieten dan MtGox. Ongetwijfeld zullen deze bedrijven nu meer succes kennen.</li>
<li>De Belgian Bitcoin Association wil Belgische gedupeerden van MtGox bijstaan door hen in contact te brengen met experten die hen de gewenste (juridische) ondersteuning kunnen bieden bij eventuele vorderingen tegen MtGox.</li>
</ol>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thomas Spaas at Flemish Investor Federation]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/02/24/thomas-spaas-at-flemish-investor-federation/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-24T22:14:43+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/02/24/thomas-spaas-at-flemish-investor-federation</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Thomas Spaas talks about Bitcoin myths, reality, hurdles &amp; opportunities at <a href="http://www.vfb.be/Vfb/Trefpunt/28951">Flemish Investor Federation</a>.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Official registration]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/02/13/official-registration/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-13T22:10:47+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/news//blog/2014/02/13/official-registration</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The <a href="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/">Belgian Bitcoin Association</a> is now officially registered as an ASBL / VZW.</p>

<p>Official charter of the association:</p>

<ul>
<li><a href="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/files/BBA-Charter-NL-20140213.pdf">Nederlandstalige versie</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/files/BBA-Charter-FR-20140213.pdf">Version française</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.bitcoinassociation.be/files/BBA-Charter-EN-20140213.pdf">English version</a></li>
</ul>


<p>Our registration number: 0546.540.263</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
